These are the test papers for this exam.
Before you start answering,
write your name, student ID, and class on the paper.
The exam time is 90 minutes.
Everyone must follow the exam rules.
Don't whisper to each other.
I, Yin Zixi,
have a 20-year-old appearance,
a 30-year-old soul,
am an uploader in the media section,
and have 3 million followers.
The overachiever who insists on doing a live stream every day.
It should be A.
But now I realize
that all these years were for nothing.
Now, every time I solve a question,
it costs me 108,600 brain cells
to awaken my distant memories.
If three are long and one is short, choose the shortest.
Stop writing and hand in your papers.
Phew, finally done.
There's still another test paper.
If two are long and two are short, choose B.
If they are uneven, choose C.
Copy and guess, and you will definitely pass.
Senior,
isn't there still 10 minutes left before the exam ends?
I am the proctor.
When I say hand it in, you hand it in.
This is unfair to our class.
Why are you students so difficult?
You never study hard.
Even with twenty extra minutes, it still wouldn't be done.
Senior.
Just talk.
Don't point at others.
I'm sorry.
Everything
started when I found this diary.
That's all for the process improvements.
I know everyone hates meetings.
Now,
let's move on to the final topic.
Damn, it's almost time to get off work.
And he's still dragging us into a meeting.
Recently, we've been trying
to integrate trending news into our livestreams.
This is the real me, Yin Zixi.
A miserable corporate slave.
Although I have three million followers,
the account belongs to the company.
Especially Yin Zixi's
report on the Cloud Data Center.
It reached number 1 on the trending list.
Everyone should take it as a reference.
It actually made the headlines.
What's going on?
Do you all find it a bit strange?
Actually,
it's not strange at all.
Because I provided this news report.
Yin Zixi getting on the trending list
was all thanks to my guidance.
Don't think that just because I'm not on the frontlines,
I don't know things.
I have a keen sense for hot topics.
This kind of news,
most people would find worthless.
Sorry.
I need to take this call.
Hurry back.
Everyone, take a close look.
Uncle He, what's wrong?
Zixi,
the report that got you trending is fake.
Fake?
This is a frame-up.
The report doesn't match the facts.
They only gave the news to your company.
I suspect someone is targeting you.
Tell your manager to come out.
You made us trend online.
You must give me an explanation today.
What's that sound?
Hello?
Yin Zixi.
Long time no see.
Do we know each other?
You have a short memory,
big streamer.
What can I do for you?
You wrote this report, didn't you?
Xihai City Cloud Data Center.
It really is about this report.
I did broadcast this news.
Who are you?
Do you know how much loss
this report brought to my client?
Miss Wen,
we can talk this over.
Yin Zixi,
don't you check the materials before reporting?
The news of Xihai University back then,
wasn't it live-streamed by you?
Me?
What you did at Xihai University,
I will never forget for the rest of my life.
I didn't know you in college.
Since you dared to report it,
you must be prepared.
This is my lawyer's letter.
I'll be waiting for you.
Two million.
Yin Zixi,
Didn't you check this report material even once?
Even though I gave you the lead
and the material,
you still should have checked it.
Otherwise, what do I need you for?
Even though I said to catch the trend...
You've said it all.
You were the one who said there was no time to check.
I might as well stream it myself.
This Wen Lingli
seems to know you.
Why don't you go plead with her
and ask her not to sue us?
Otherwise, get out of here.
Your operating account has nothing to do with our company.
You handle this compensation yourself.
Don't drag us down with you,
big streamer.
Wh-What are you doing?
What am I doing?
I'm hitting a scumbag like you.
Yin Zixi!
What are you waiting for?
I will solve this myself.
The account that belongs to me,
I will get it back myself.
Do you know why Wen Lingli is targeting you?
Why is she targeting me?
Xihai University news.
I've almost gone through all the news about this university.
I can't remember anything.
I'm doomed now.
A washed-up streamer is ruthlessly framed after offending a big conglomerate.
After going bankrupt, no one dares to hire her.
From then on, she begins a life of wandering.
Wow, what a great harvest.
Hmm, no, no.
Wake up.
Yin Zixi, wake up.
What on earth am I thinking about?
Is anyone there?
Help!
Can anyone help me?
Granny, I'm coming.
Granny, are you alright?
I...
I'm fine.
Okay.
Hey, miss.
Why do you look so familiar to me?
Do I?
Oh.
I remember now.
I saw you in that
trash.
Me? Trash?
Yeah.
Wait here.
Look.
It's you, right?
This is me.
Why don't I remember this at all?
Ah!
What are you yelling for?
Don't you know people have classes during the day?
Are you crazy?
You're already in college.
Why are you still wearing a school uniform?
Sorry.
Isn't that Wen Lingli?
Why does she seem a bit different?
Excuse me.
You saw the activity
on this banner, right?
Xihai University 2016.
Ah.
October 10, 2016.
I time-traveled!
Diary.
Today I saw Wen Lingli bullying a classmate.
I really couldn't stand it.
I stepped forward to stop her.
For this endorsement activity,
can you not participate?
Stop! Let go of that girl.
I've tolerated you for a long time.
Making such a fuss here.
Since you've already let her go,
I'll be leaving now.
Assistant Casting Director Xi Chongjing
Props Assistant Li Kunxiao
Grip Truck Yi Mingle
Yitong